WAYE 8:05时段新闻
WA YE news time, 8:05.
今天局部地区多云 风和日暖 最高气温80华氏度(27度)
It's gonna be partly cloudy, breezy and warm today with highs around 80.
此时的Baltimore 晴空万里
Right now in Baltimore, sunny skies.
下面是我的晨间最爱
And here's one of my morning favorites.
嘿Ott!  Santo Rey号误点了哈?
Yo, Ott. Santo Rey's late?
昨晚Hampton锚地起风了
Squall last night off of Hampton Roads.
76-72呼叫总台
76-72 KGA.
这是总台 请讲 76-72
KGA, go ahead, 76-72.
请通知凶案组和法医办公室 Patapsco码头航站处捞起一具浮尸
Notify Homicide and the OCME. We got a floater at Patapsco Terminal.
收到
Copy that.
火线重案组 第二季 第十二集 风中码头
The Wire S02E12 Port in a Storm
"Way Down in the Hole" 演唱:Tom Waits
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* He's got the fire and the fury *
* At his command *
* Well you don't have to worry *
* If you hold on to Jesus hand *
* We'll all be safe from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls *
* Just gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
"生意 总是生意"  ---"希腊人"
Vondopoulos房子里没有发现?
Nothing at Vondopoulos's house?
他不会回去了
He's not going back.
他把奔驰车和我们的GPS 丢弃在市中心的车库里
He's dumped his Benz and our GPS device in the downtown garage.
手机也停了
He's off the cell phones.
也没有再发过希腊语的短信
And there's no text messaging in Greek either.
或许是突袭 或许是跟踪 让他躲了起来
The raids, the follow, one or both sent him underground.
这个家伙 Stephen Rados 他是什么来头?
This guy, Stephen Rados? What's he?
是他租了和Vondopoulos会面的旅馆房间
He rented the hotel room for the meet with Vondopoulos.
但是之后发上退房了
But checked out right after.
Fitzhugh在所有数据库里 检索了他的信息
Fitzhugh's running him through every database.
目前为止 只有一张华盛顿的驾照
So far, nothing but a driver's license in D.C.
Lester 凶案组找你 二号线
Lester. Homicide for you, line 2.
也许Sobotka认识他
Maybe Sobotka knows him.
等今天Sobotka来了 也许能透露给我们关于希腊人的所有底细
When Sobotka comes in today, maybe he gives us a line on every last Greek.
我是Freamon
Freamon here.
从暴力罪犯追踪署那 传来了大约13张传真
Thirteen or so coming across the fax from VICAP.
所有都是无名氏
All of them John Does.
而这只是在中大西洋地区(美国东岸)发现的无头无手的尸体
And that's just headless and handless in the mid-Atlantic region.
如果你要扩展到全国 你得做好收到四打子的思想准备
If you wanna go nationwide, you'll be up over four dozen.
- 我操 - 我能说什么呢 小子
-Fuck me. -What can I tell you, kiddo?
我们是在维护一个世风日下的治安
We are policing a culture in moral decline.
那么你想自己过来拿
So, you want to come get these?
还是我派个警员给你送到东南区?
Or should I have a uniform run them over to Southeast?
- 把它们送过来吧 - 行
-Run them over to Southeast. -Okay.
- 坐 - 不了
-Have a seat. -I can't.
还得马上回去料理生意
Gotta get back out there, take care of business.
只是想确认他们有好好治疗你
Just wanted to make sure they were treating you right.
差不多 起码我能起来看书了
Making the most of it. I'm catching up on my reading at least.
我只是想让你知道 你有我们呢
I just want to let you know that we got your back.
你瞧 无论是谁干的 我们都会找出来
You know, whoever did this, we'll find them.
我们会为你报仇 你明白吗
We got you, you understand?
谢谢你的美意 但是不必了
I appreciate the offer, but that won't be necessary.
请转告Barksdale 此次事件
Inform Mr. Barksdale that any obligation...
令他觉得应当承担任何的责任
he feels he might have with regards to this incident...
都无需再计较 包括我们的协议
it's absolved, along with our agreement.
我说的是...
All I'm saying is-
我非常明白你的意思
I understand perfectly well what you're saying.
但是我告诉你的是 我自己可以对付他们
What i am saying to you is,I will take care of them myself.
"他们"?
Them?
谁袭击了你?
Who came at you?
谢谢你的关心
Thank you for your concern.
不要冲动 Nick 不要冲动
Easy, Nick. Easy.
我要杀了他们 那些该死的希腊杂种!
I'm gonna kill them. Fucking Greek bastards.
他妈的不要拦我!
Get out of my fucking way!
放开我! 你们他妈的都闪开!
Get off of me! Fuck all of you!
他曾处处罩着你们 你们现在却撒手不管
He was there for all of you, and now you're nowhere for him.
那你它妈的打算怎么做?
What the fuck you gonna do?
找把枪? 当土匪?
Get a gun? Go play gangster?
像你那该死的表弟?
Like your fucking cousin?
我们走吧
Let's go.
她吸了什么啊 伙计?
What was she firing, yo?
"脏弹"(新毒品的名字)和一管红帽
Dirty Bomb, with a red-top chaser.
该死的 "炸弹"就是"炸弹"啊
Damn, yo. The bomb is the bomb.
机会在敲门 给我把好风
Opportunity knocking. Keep a lookout.
他居然打劫了救护车
He just boosted the whole fucking truck.
风把得真好 Johnny
Good looking out, Johnny.
起码我记得打电话了
At least I remembered to call.
身中数刀
Stabbed repeatedly.
躯干 下腹 并且割了他的喉咙  万无一失
Torso, abdomen, and they cut his throat to be sure.
单刃刀 他也反抗了
Single-edge blade. He fought, too.
双手都有防御伤
Defense wounds on both hands.
双脚被绑
Ligature on both legs.
用什么重物让他沉尸海底 但重物在水中散落了
Weighed him down with something, but it slipped off in the drink.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
去它的 这个Sobotka小子知道有逮捕令
Fuck it. This Sobotka kid knows there's a warrant.
管他自不自首 谁在乎
He either turns himself in or not. Who gives a fuck?
要么我们现在抓他回局里 要么等他带着律师去警局报道
Either we get to him now and roll him, or he comes into the district with a lawyer.
他带着律师来自首 那一切都好谈了
He comes in with a lawyer, he's less likely to go for something in the box.
你听着真像McNulty了
You sound like McNulty now.
要是继续跟这些家伙耗在他们的案子上 我们永远别想出人头地了
We stay with these guys on their cases, we ain't never gonna get no respect.
你知道的
You know this.
我想好了 等专案组结了 我会马上回缉毒队
I figure when the detail's over, I go back to straight narcotics.
希望能进Dawson那组 找个新头头
Try to get over to Dawson's shift, find a new rabbi.
你呢?
What about you?
不知道
Don't know.
我是说 你得承认 Daniels待我们不薄
I mean, you gotta admit, Daniels has been okay for us.
我是说 他很罩自己的手下
I mean, he's there for his troops.
Daniels
Daniels.
- 你是在跟开玩笑吧 - 我刚从案发现场来
-You gotta be shitting me. -I just came from the crime scene.
他曾投案来配合调查
He was coming in as a cooperator.
交代他曾帮助走私的贩毒和卖淫集团
Offering up the drug-and-prostitution ring he'd been smuggling for.
和黑帮同流合污 下场就是被抹脖子
The guy lays down with gangsters, gets up with his throat cut.
我都要为这杂种感到难过了
Almost feel sorry for the son of a bitch.
你对Sobotka所料不错
You were right about Sobotka.
案子进展神速 我已经让Burrell答应
Case had enough legs on it that I've got Burrell committed...
让我的人自成一组 独立于刑侦大队之外
to keeping my crew together as a major case squad working out of CID.
如果你打算起诉他...
If you are gonna charge him....
我绝对会告死他
I'm gonna charge his narrow ass.
你要告你的女婿?
You're gonna do your son-in-law?
你觉得我没告诉过她 别嫁给那个脑瘫的杂种吗?
You don't think I didn't tell her not to marry that brain-dead son of a bitch?
我跟你说实话吧 警长
I'll tell you the truth, Major.
每个人都目睹了那一拳头
Everyone who saw the punch wrote on it.
他们都看到Prez出手了 毋庸置疑
And they've all got Prez throwing the punch, no question.
但是他们也目击到你 称呼一位下属为...
But they've also got you addressing a subordinate officer as a....
什么呢? "蠢蛋"?
What was it? A shitbird?
操你的
Fuck you.
这是Baltimore警察局 不是Roland公园街头茶坊
This is the Baltimore Police Department, not the Roland Park Ladies' Tea.
我只是说 其他探员...
I'm just saying, the other detectives...
那些个联邦特工 他们都写下了目睹的一切
the FBI agents, they gotta write it the way it happened.
我是说 我当然可以让我的人为你改口 但是那些联邦探员...
I mean, I could probably get my own people to cheat it for you, but the FBl....
你知道他们多么耿直
You know how tight-assed they are.
让Roland Pryzbylewski 在东南警局办公室里
Roland Pryzbylewski rides the Southeastern desk...
值两个月的夜班
on midnight shift for two months.
期间 他必须写私人道歉信
During which time he writes a personal letter of apology...
给所有目击他动手的人
to everyone seen that punch throwed.
在信里 他必须写清楚 自己的举动是多么软弱无能
In which he makes it absolutely clear that it was a penny-cheap sucker punch...
理应受到一位真正警察的训诫
that would've got his ass kicked in by a real police...
但是对方因为顾忌到女儿的感受 而没有这么做
except for the fact that I have my daughter's feelings to consider.
然后他就可以过来 当面再对我说一遍
And then he can come up here and say the same to my face...
之后 他想留在你的小组里自毁前程
and after that, if he wants to piss his career away in your unit...
我才不会多管闲事
I could give a hairy-ass fuck.
请吧 警督
Lieutenant.
Rod 那东西该放在附件里
Rod, that shit goes into a supplemental.
- 你不能把证人写在概要里 - 长官
-You don't put witnesses on a face sheet. -Officer.
你们这有东西给Freamon吗 是凶杀科送过来的
You got something for Freamon? Homicide sent it over.
长官 我儿子想来自首 接受对他的逮捕令
Officer, my son wants to turn himself in on a warrant.
人人都在发话 可惜没人在听
Everybody talks, nobody listens.
Mike 那混蛋再打电话过来 就说我去厕所了
Mike, that asshole calls back, I'm in the shitter.
- 那么我有什么能效劳的 先生们? - 你们有张指控我贩毒的逮捕令
-Now what can I do for you, gents? -You got a warrant on me for drugs.
- 我是来自首的 - 一张东南区警局发的逮捕令?
-I'm turning myself in. -A Southeastern warrant?
他来自首 愿意全力配合
He's surrendering. He's gonna cooperate in any way he can.
- 你是叫什么名字 - Sobotka...Nicholas Sobotka
-What name am I looking for? -Sobotka. Nicholas Sobotka.
偷吗啡? 从一辆市救护车上?
Morphine? From a city ambo?
为这事来找我 你真该害臊
You should be ashamed to be calling me on this one.
- 尸体被发现了 - 我看到了 在电视上
-The body came up. -I saw, on the television.
我们很小心地沉了他的尸首
We weighted him down pretty goddamn good...
但是水流又把他冲了回来
but the water just coughed him back up.
不走运而已
Bad luck, that's all.
我承认 Sergei会做得更好
Sergei would've done better, I admit.
Niko 那个侄子 他现在是知情人
Niko, the nephew. By now he knows.
我们的人在候着他 但是警察也是
Our people wait for him, but so do the police.
我觉得...
I am thinking...
眼下我们也束手无策
there's nothing to be done at this point.
他说了就说了吧
What he says, he says.
他知道我的名字 但那不是我的真名
He knows my name. But my name is not my name.
你呢?
And you?
对他们来说 你只是"希腊人"
To them, you're only "The Greek."
当然了 我甚至不是真的希腊人
And, of course, I'm not even Greek.
那我们走吧
So we go.
但首先还有生意上的事要处理
But there's a little business to do first.
这个星期还有货到港
There's a shipment on the docks this week.
- 150公斤 - 但是没人去拿
-One hundred and fifty kilograms. -And no one to pick it up.
不只是Sergei 我也想念Frank
Not just Sergei, I miss Frank, too.
我们没法让集装箱消失 但是也许我们可以派个人
We can't disappear the can. But maybe we send someone.
把它合法地移出码头
Bring it off the docks, legitimate.
这些天我们去过的地方 似乎都会撞见警察
Everywhere we go these days, we seem to be walking into police.
这是在暗示我们
This is telling us something.
你要让1500万的货烂在码头上?
You're going to leave 15 million tholaria to rot on the pier?
太可惜了
(speaks greek)
"那些羊羔大难临头还不知"(出自圣经)人得学会何时放手
Lambs go to slaughter. A man, he learns when to walk away.
不 我们得走了
No, we go.
通知其他人
Call the others in.
告诉他们不必再等了
Let them know there is no longer any point.
撤
Dmitri.
不等了?
We don't wait?
我们的朋友还在那儿?
Our friends are still there, no?
- 还在 - 那撤吧
-Still here. -Then go.
Sobotka投案来配合调查?
Sobotka was a cooperator?
我们昨天和他进行了初步讨论
We had preliminary discussions with him yesterday.
他同意今天带律师来 可惜...
He agreed to post today with a lawyer, but instead....
那案子还剩下什么?
So what's left of the case?
我们把录音带里的人都抓了 希望能查到一些弃尸的真凶
We've pulled in everyone caught up in the wiretaps, save for a couple bodies.
尚有一名我们认为是团伙 二号头目的嫌犯未缉捕
We left the man we think is the number two for the operation...
希望他能帮我们引出一号头目
on the street, hoping he'd lead us to number one.
有我们的人盯着他吗?
We have people on him?
目前他下落不明
He's out of pocket at the moment.
最后一次是看到他离开了市区的旅馆 但是我们预计他会再度露面
Last seen leaving a downtown hotel, but we expect he'll resurface.
那工会的人呢?
And the union people?
考虑到Sobotka已死 案犯缩小到他的一两个下手
With Sobotka dead, the case right now is limited to a subordinate or two.
但是我们在意的是工会
But the important thing for us is the union.
要么他们放弃现在的领导班子
Either they jettison their current leadership...
否则我们有足够理由 申请取缔当地工会
or we have enough to get that local decertified.
结果只剩下我和那14具尸体
Leaving only me and my 14 bodies.
我们什么时候能谈那事?
When do we get to that bit of business?
Daniels警督 二号线 Freamon探员一定要我接进来
Lt. Daniels? Line 2. Det. Freamon insisted I put him through.
十有八九 Frank Sobotka本会谈到
In all likelihood, Frank Sobotka was going to speak to that.
可惜现在我们回到了原点 很遗憾
Now, we're a step back, sorry to say.
- Sobotka来自首了 - 那个侄子?
-Sobotka came in. -The nephew?
是的 他来招供了
Yeah, he flipped.
拜托 Bubs 如果你想脱罪 你得表现得更好些
Come on, Bubs. You gotta do better if you wanna walk on this.
- 八卦一下那些杀人犯如何? - 那些人怎么了?
-How about some murders? -How about them?
这些日子他们在西区不杀人了?
They're not killing people in West Baltimore these days?
都没动静了
Been quiet.
除了有个小年轻
Except for that mess with that young boy who got hit...
被飞进窗户的流弹打中 没别的了
with the stray through the window, ain't been nothing.
- 那这件事呢? - 我不知道是谁
-How about that? -I ain't got nothing on that one.
不过是两帮人马在街头火拼
It's just two crews beefing over a corner.
你知道吗 Bubs? 你等着进监狱吧
You know what, Bubs? You going to jail.
你说监狱干嘛?
How you gonna talk about going to jail?
你听见了 Johnny?
You hearing this, Johnny?
就像是我们过去没半点关系似的 就像我们不是朋友似的
Like we ain't got history in this room. Like we ain't friends or nothing.
当初你进医院时 我可是担心死你了
When you was up in that hospital, all I did was worry.
"Kima呢? 我的姑娘怎么了?"
"What about Kima? What's up with my girl?"
我很高兴又能见到你
I'm just happy to see you're up in the mix...
你却跟我说什么破监狱
and you talking about jail and shit.
太无情了 姑娘 真的
That's too cold, girl, damn.
嘿 嘿 记得那个高楼区的东区小子 受枪伤的事吗?
Remember that Eastsider got shot in the high-rises, right?
你还记得那事 对吧?
You remember that shit, right?
我是说 你就在现场啊 Bubbles
I mean, you were right there, Bubbles.
那算什么破事 不过是个小子中了空心弹而已
That wasn't shit. Boy got hit with a rat shot, that all.
- 你在说什么? - 那个叫Cheese的
-Who you talking about? -Boy named Cheese.
他和其他几个东区的家伙 入主了公房区
Him and the other Eastsiders moved into the Terrace...
从Stringer Bell的手下那接管了几栋楼
took over a couple towers from the Stringer Bell's boys.
结果有个厉害的打领结的黑鬼来了 把他赶回来了老家
Then some crazy-ass bow-tie nigger came in and chased his ass home.
发生了什么事?
And what happened?
领结先生 他赶走了他们
Mr. Bow Tie, he ran them off.
他告诉那些东区的蠢蛋 "那些楼是属于Avon的"
He told them Eastsider fools, "Them towers belong to Avon."
不过后来他就再没出现
But then he ain't come back no more.
现在那些东区的人又跑了回来 成了那里的固定卖家
Now them Eastsiders are back up in there steady slinging.
我是说 这又不算打仗
I mean, it ain't like a war or nothing.
就像是Stringer Bell和他们在共享
It's like Stringer Bell and them are sharing.
共享?
Sharing?
你们对这些了如指掌?
You guys are on all of it?
你身边坐着一位公共辩护人 Sobotka先生
You have a public defender sitting next to you, Mr. Sobotka.
如果你对此次合作有任何疑问...
If there's anything about this deal you don't understand-
他们杀了我的叔叔
They killed my uncle.
我只要跟你们谈就行了
I don't need to talk to no one but you people.
你怎么知道是他们做的?
How do you know they did it?
我告诉他...
I told....
当大家都被捕之后 Spiros打电话给我
Spiros calls me after everybody's getting arrested, right?
告诉我 他希望我们不要乱说话
Tells me he wants us to keep our mouths shut...
但是Frank叔叔 他说他不会那么做
but Uncle Frank, he says he ain't gonna.
说他要跟警察全交代了
Says he's gonna go talk to the police.
Spiros说如果我们能保密...
Spiros says that if we keep quiet...
他可以帮助我的堂弟 Zig 你们知道吗?
they can help my cousin, Zig, you know?
Spiros说...
And now Spiros is saying that...
我不知道 那小孩 那个还没有死的...
I don't know, the kid, the one that didn't die...
那个被枪打中的小子
the one that got shot...
他愿意作证 那枪不是Zig的
he's gonna say that the gun, it wasn't Zig's.
是那个Glekas先开的枪 不算Zig的错
That Glekas pulled the gun, and it wasn't really Zig's fault.
所以你叔叔为了谈这事 跑去见了他们?
So your uncle went to meet them and talk about that?
在Key桥下
Under the Key Bridge.
今天早上 我看到他的车还在那儿
I seen his car was still there this morning.
我看到的时候就料到了
I seen that, I fucking knew.
如果他们为了灭口而杀了你叔叔 他们很可能...
If they killed your uncle to shut him up, they probably-
也来杀我 对吧?
Wanna kill me, too?
操
Shit!
我本打算去桥下
I was gonna go down with him to the bridge.
和他一起去
I was gonna go down there with him.
他不让...
He wouldn't....
你也参与了走私吗?
You were involved in the smuggling?
我们不知道那些女孩
We didn't know about the girls.
那些被发现的女孩
Them girls that got found?
- 我们不知道她们在里面 - 你们以为是毒品?
-We didn't know there were girls in there. -You thought it was drugs?
毒品 赃物 随便
Drugs, stolen shit, whatever.
我们收钱 只管从码头 把集装箱转移出来而已
We got paid by the can to creep shit off the docks. That's all.
但是你也从"希腊人"那 拿到毒品 进行兜售 对吧?
That and selling the drugs that you got from The Greek, too, right?
这是你堂弟签了字的口供
That's your cousin's signed statement.
他自首的时候说了买枪的事
He put himself in, talked about buying the gun.
从当铺买的凭证也在
The bill of sale from the pawn shop is in there, too.
就算有第二个受害人出来佐证 那也无关紧要了
It wouldn't have mattered if the second victim had backed up on his story.
你堂弟的牢坐定了
Your cousin was locked in.
你叔叔昨天就坐在 你现在坐的这个位置上...
Your uncle was sitting yesterday right where you're sitting now...
他愿意交代一切 只要我们放弃对你贩毒的指控
ready to give us everything, if we made the drug charges go away for you.
也许让你的堂弟关进一个 比Eager街监狱更好的地方
And maybe got your cousin to a better lock-up than Eager Street.
你也看见了 我们愿意遵守这个约定...
As you can see, we're willing to honor that deal...
即使你的叔叔不能再做到了
even if it didn't happen for your uncle.
Spiros是那个主脑
Spiros was the main guy.
他告诉我和Frank 要让哪个集装箱消失...
He told me and Frank which cans to disappear...
而我的毒品生意 也是他牵线搭桥
and then when it came to me and the drugs, he was the one that hooked that up, too.
那个希伯来人 是他们的毒贩
The lsraeli, he was their drug guy.
我通过他来补货...
I went through him for all my re-ups...
直到他们让我去找"麦克白"McArdle 你们知道Mike吧?
until they passed me off to White Mike McArdle. You know Mike?
看来是的了
Guess you do.
"双G"负责销赃
Double G was in charge of stolen shit.
任何我们能从码头带走的东西 都会送到他的店里
Anything we could lift from the docks went straight to his store...
但是他死了 所以多说无益 不是吗
but he's dead, so why am I wasting your time, right?
她? 我不认识
Her, I don't know.
我的叔叔 你们都知道了
My uncle, you know about him.
我不知道你们怎么会把"马面"的照片也放上去
I don't know why you got Horse's picture up there.
"马面"什么都不知道 我可以作证
Horse don't know shit. I'll testify to that.
那俄罗斯人呢?
What about the Russian?
他替他们开车
He drove for them.
所有运离码头的东西 都是经他的手
Anything that had to come off the docks, he was their guy.
但是我也觉得 如果要收拾谁
But I also got the feeling that if somebody had to get hurt...
也会是他出面动手
he was probably going to be around for that part of it, too.
为什么你会这么觉得?
Why did you think that?
Sergei 他行事就是如此
Sergei, he just carried it like that.
而且 那些女孩死在集装箱里以后..
And also, after them girls died in the can...
他们告诉我 那个坏了事的混蛋
they told me that whoever fucked that up...
他们已经在费城抓住了
they had already got to in Philly.
他们说害死那些姑娘的家伙已经死了
They said that whoever did that to them girls was dead.
他们是怎么说的?
And how did they say it?
他们说...我不知道...
They just said, I don't know...
那个你们要找的人...
that the guy that you all was looking for...
是个"死"胡同
he was a dead end.
- 死胡同? - 是的
-A dead end? -Yeah.
他们说是在费城
In Philly, they said.
西装男是谁?
Who's the suit?
你确定?
You sure?
我们知道Spiros上面还有人
We know that someone is above your man Spiros.
一个他曾联系过的人
Someone he was in communication with.
是的 "希腊人"
Yeah, The Greek.
当然 我知道你是指谁 可惜我不知道名字和其他
Sure, I know who you mean. I mean, I don't have a name or nothing.
这个穿着西装的...
The man in the suit...
那个和Vondopoulos 一起出现在照片里的
the man with Vondopoulos in the photograph.
不是"希腊人"?
That's not The Greek?
"希腊人"是这位
That's The Greek right there.
这个家伙?
That the guy?
还行 他认出了一个东区人
He picked out an Eastsider, all right.
Cheese是"建议乔"的手下
Cheese runs with Proposition Joe's mob.
我曾听说 他在Ashland有几个据点
Had a few corners off of Ashland, last I heard.
- 裁决如何? - 他对我们有用
-What's the verdict? -He did good for us.
- 所以不管我的事了? - 我欠你一个人情 Sanny
-So I'm out the stat? -I owe you one, Sanny.
- 他们都是? - 是的 那是他的跟班
-Both of them? -Yeah, that one's his valet.
我能用你的厕所吗?
Can I use your bathroom?
他妈的没门 滚出去
Fuck, no. Get out of here.
Bubs 最后一个问题 高楼区的货怎么样?
Bubs, one last question. How's product in the Towers?
原本很烂 现在很正
It was shit, now it's right.
查到了这个家伙 在华盛顿的联邦法院电脑里
Found this guy. Federal court computer down in D.C.
但不是坏的记录
But not in a bad way.
华盛顿有名的"驻京办"聚集地 有各种游说公司
他是在K街的律师
He's a K Street lawyer down there.
所以西装男只是个西装男?
So the suit was only a suit?
另一方面 我的伙计 这是从海外发来的
On the other hand, my friend, this is from overseas.
Adriatica号上的一个集装箱 后天将登陆Patapsco码头
A can on the Adriatica, which docks the day after tomorrow at Patapsco.
伪造的法国勒阿弗尔港货单
Fake manifest out of Le Havre.
你们的人真是神通广大
You people got reach.
我们可是花了30万的工资工时
That's about $300,000 in man-hours we're holding here.
对他有什么打算?
What's the plan for him?
你得打电话给检察院 要求证人保护计划
You gotta call the US Attorney about witness protection.
包括他的女人和孩子
We're rounding up his girl and kid.
最好能暗中进行
It's best we keep this as quiet as we can.
我们已经损失了一位合作人
We already lost one cooperator.
是找你的
It's for you.
Daniels
Daniels.
警督 Fitzhugh来接受保护的证人 我们也让他的女朋友和孩子加入了
Lieutenant, Fitzhugh's calling for WITSEC, and we're pulling in the girlfriend and kid.
行 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
联邦调查局
FBl.
这是Baltimore分局的 Terrence Fitzhugh特工
This is Special Agent Terrence Fitzhugh, Baltimore field office.
- 我可以和Koutris特工谈谈吗? - 谁?
-May I speak with Agent Koutris, please? -Who?
Koutris特工
Agent Koutris.
他已经不在San Diego分局了
He's no longer with the San Diego field office.
那他去哪儿了?
Where's he at?
你可以试试华盛顿总部 反恐大队
You could try headquarters in Washington. Counterterrorism.
反恐大队? 多久了?
Counterterrorism? For how long?
那我得查查 但我肯定 他去那儿已经有一年多了
I'd have to check, but I'm sure he's been gone from here more than a year.
要么他在五分钟之内回家 要么我就饮弹自尽
Either he comes home in the next five minutes, or I eat my gun.
我只是说 这可不是...
I'm just saying, this is not the way...
我们在西Baltimore学来的本事
me and you learned how to do it in West Baltimore.
它妈的远了去了
Not by a fucking long shot!
要么你儿子在一小时内去自首...
Either your son surrenders within the hour...
要么我们警察一天两次 把这掀个底朝天
or all the police will come crashing through this door twice a day...
直到你们乖乖就范 你听到我说的了吗?
for as long as it takes you people to get the message. You hear me?
我们会早一次 晚一次 撞开这扇门 掀翻你全家
We will take this door once in the morning and once at night, and toss your house...
直到所有家具都只剩下三条腿
until there isn't any furniture with more than three legs left on it.
你听见了吗?
You hear me?
长官 我的儿子昨晚已经去警局自首了
Officer, my son turned himself in to the police last night.
就在东南警局 当时还有一个探员在场
At Southeastern. A detective was there at the time.
Lester Freamon警探 刑侦部凶杀科
搞什么鸟 走
Motherfucker, c'mon.
不要用电话
Don't use the phone.
会有个特工在外守卫 如果你要去哪儿 带上他
There'll be an agent posted outside. If you go anywhere, go with him.
什么垃圾地方啊
What a dump.
你不是想有个我们自己的地方吗?
You wanted us to get a place, right?
如果他们在费城抓住了他...
If they got to him in Philly...
那他们很可能在那弃尸 不是吗?
then they probably dumped the body in that area, right?
何必拖着一个没头的躯干到处跑呢
No use in dragging a headless torso around further than you need.
我的天
Good God.
我猜肯定在某个地方还有个警探
I bet you there's a police detective somewhere else...
盯着桌上一堆脑袋的照片看呢
Iooking at a table full of heads right now.
我们从船上搜到的东西里 有没有什么照片?
In that stuff that we took off the ship, did we keep any photos?
有几张跳船家伙的照片
Couple of pictures of one guy that left his gear, yeah.
都在物证科
They're at ECU.
你们该上路了 务必在办公室关门前到
You two should get on the road. Get up there before the offices close.
你们都去哪儿了?
Where y'all been at?
不过我说 Butchie 这事有蹊跷
I'm saying, though, Butchie, something just ain't feel right.
那家伙根本不知道我在说什么
The man didn't even know what I was saying.
所以我就放过了他
So I just eased off.
- 你觉得那大哥玩了我? - 不
- You think brother played me? - No.
如果这些年里你连谎言都看不透...
Y'all can't read lying eyes after all these years...
那现在我就是跟个死人说话了
then I'd be talking to a dead man.
你说是Stringer告诉你
You saying Stringer told you...
那个老兄和你Brandon小弟的死有关?
the brother had something to do with your boy Brandon?
是的
Yeah.
但是我却听说 Mouzone大兄最近都是呆在北边
Near as I know, Brother Mouzone spends most of his time up north.
纽约 费城
New York and Philly.
如果当初Avon雇他来做掉你
If Avon contracted him to get at you...
那除非你们狭路相逢 否则他不会善罢甘休
the brother wouldn't have stop coming until you two were bumped.
是我的错
It's my fault.
我当初就该回绝了"建议乔"
I should've said no to Prop Joe from the get-go.
Avon的父亲恶贯满盈 他的儿子也好不到哪儿去
Avon's father was plain evil, and the son ain't no better.
Stringer也是 我们现在都看清楚了
Neither is Stringer, now that we making a list.
我要好好教训一下Stringer
I'm going hard after Stringer.
我猜现在要让你打消这个念头 已经不可能了
No point in trying to talk you back down, I suppose.
你当我账房多久了 居然还会这么问我?
You been my bank for how long and gonna ask me something like that?
你打算怎么报复他?
How you gonna get at him?
我还不知道 Butch
I don't even know, Butch.
得花时间想一想
Take some time and think on it.
不过有件事是肯定的 此仇不报非君子 你明白吗?
One thing for sure, though, the man got to be got, you feel me?
你觉得呢 Butch?
What you see, Butch?
太多的恩怨了 孩子
Too much, boy.
多得算不清
Too damn much.
一夜之间发生了很多事
A lot happened overnight.
我们没有
Not to us.
- 瞧 这不是针对个人... - 太对了 没错
- Look, this isn't personal... - Fucking-A, right.
我们甚至不算这组里的"人" 我们只是给你们做牛做马
We're not even people in this unit. We're your goddamn pack mules.
"监视这房子 押送这个混蛋 等待那一个"
"Sit on this house, transport this mope, wait for that one."
这是工作的一部分
That's part of the job.
我记得的工作 是去追捕毒贩
The job had a little more rip-and-run to it, the way I remember it.
这些案子远不止这样
These cases are more than that.
我们利用电话监听和记录 把疑犯送进监狱
We're putting people in jail with phone taps and typewriters.
那么你是说我们还没这本事?
So you're saying we ain't up to it.
我看到西区的Colvin警长 招募警监的海报
I saw on the postings that Major Colvin needs a sergeant in the Western.
机动小队 没错的话 我已经是带衔的了
Flex squad. And the last time I checked, I had stripes.
东区 西区
Eastside, Westside.
阿狗阿猫 同床而眠(上句是"猪猡上天 地狱结冰")
Cats and dogs, sleeping together.
该死 我有事要迟到了
Shit. I'm late for something.
你说你要找所有那天来码头的人?
You say you want everybody that came on the port that day?
不 我们只是在查异常情况 很可能是发生在晚上
No, we're looking for anything out of the ordinary. Probably at night.
哦 不寻常的 你应该早说
Oh, unusual. You should've said so.
- 你之前要求的是... - 那是我们...
- What you asked for before... - That's what we...
你说得对 长官 一点没错 看看是不是有异常情况
You're right, sir, absolutely right. Just see if there's anything like that.
不 我只看到一切正常
Nope, all I got is usual.
好吧 只要你能给我们一个那天晚上
All right. Any way you could give us the name...
在码头巡逻的保安名字
of the security officer that was on this pier that night?
再说一遍那天是几号
What was that date again?
2月5日
February 5.
大西洋灯号在当晚六点靠港
You had the Atlantic Light on that pier from 6:00 p.m.
那是Walt...Walt Stokes
That was Walt. Walt Stokes.
他今晚上班吗?
Is he working tonight?
今天是星期四 Walt星期四不上班
It's Tuesday. Walt's off on Tuesdays.
你们找Walt干嘛?
What do you want Walt for?
瞧瞧他能不能认出这些人
See if he can make any of these.
也许没什么用
Wouldn't do much good.
恐怕Walt的反应还不及我们剩下的人
Afraid Walt's not as up to speed as the rest of us.
不过看在你们大老远来的份上...
Seeing as you've come all this way, though...
也许你们想看一眼录像带
you might want to have a look-see at the videotapes.
300元买辆婴儿车?
$300 for a stroller?
我知道 我知道 比你第一辆车还贵 对吧?
I know, I know. Cost more than your first car, right?
一辆老爷车 对吧?
A hooptie, no doubt?
我们也会很需要这些
We're so gonna need one of these.
看这个 Kima
Look at this, Kima.
Blue's Clues(一档婴儿早教节目)出品的饮料杯托
Blue's Clues juice box holder.
如果宝宝连个小纸盒都拿不住 那我们就真有麻烦了
If the kid can't hold on to a little old box without no help, we got problems.
好吧 听着
Okay, listen.
这孩子会从我肚子里生出来 从此以后都会需要我们两人的照顾
This baby is gonna come out of my belly and need both of us, forever.
你明白吗
You understand?
也许你还没怎么当真
I mean, it may not be real for you yet.
但是 该死的 我已经有了切身感受
But, goddamn it, it's real for me.
Nick
Nick.
Nicky
Nicky.
以后会怎样 Nikcy?
What's gonna happen, Nicky?
Nicky?
被架在那的集装箱
That can on the fifth wheel there.
计划里 它是个烫手货 但是没人来领
By the plan, it's a hot box, but there's no one on a pick-up.
- 从哪儿来的? - 法国的勒阿弗尔
- Where's it from? - Le Havre, France.
去它的 扔了它
Fuck it, then. Dump her.
Lester 在仓库电话停用之前
Lester, the drug talk coming from Proposition Joe's people...
"建议乔"的人打进来要毒品的电话
before the warehouse phone came down.
通常数量都很稳定 对吗?
Those were for steady re-ups, right?
那条线我们没有监听太久 不过是的 连续三周都是
We weren't up on that wire long, but, yeah, three weeks in a row.
- 有多少? - 开始是5到6个"按摩沙发"
- How much? - Five or six La-Z-Boys at a clip, to start.
最后一次他们打给Eton 在电话里要了12个
Last call to Eton's cell phone, the re-up went to 12.
他加倍了他的提货量 要到12公斤?
He doubles his re-up to 12 kilos?
就是它
That's her right there.
不过他们没有玩猫腻
They ain't doing the dirt, though.
小队长 盯紧那个我们通知的集装箱
Team leader, keep an eye on that can till we post.
收到
Copy.
很遗憾听到我的朋友Sergei的事
Sorry to hear about my boy Sergei.
还有Eton
Eton, too.
你失去了几个不错的手下
You lost some good people.
很快会有新面孔出现
There'll be some new faces soon.
一星期左右 他们会来找你
A week or so. They'll find you.
以及其他我们的合作对象
Just as they'll find the others that work with us.
一个星期?
A week?
你的好东西可不够我撑到那个时候
I ain't got enough of your good shit to last much past that.
在你走之前 有什么可以先垫垫饥吗?
You got anything to lay off before you leave?
最后一船东西丢了
The last shipment is lost.
丢了? 你什么意思?
Lost? How you mean?
也许被警察盯上了
The police may be sitting on it.
你确定?
You ain't sure?
以后还会有的
There's more where that came from.
总是还会有的
Always, there is more.
那么好吧
All right, then.
我等你的新人来找我
I'm gonna let your new people find me.
一路平安
Have a safe trip.
你说你要去哪儿?
Where you say you off to again?
这箱12包 那箱15包
There's 12 in this, 15 in that.
如果剩下的都是这么个装法
And if the rest of them holds this same pattern...
那码头上大约有200公斤的纯货
Maybe 200 kilos of raw left on the pier.
希腊人绝对是逃之夭夭了
The Greeks are definitely in the wind.
我们成了无头苍蝇
And we are in the dark.
你想让我们把它送到海关仓库 还是怎样?
You want us to take it down to the customs shed, or what?
不 你把它封好了 监视它
No, you're gonna seal it up and sit on it.
如果我们走运 几天内会就有人来申领
If we're lucky, someone will come calling in a day or so.
你们能走运吗?
You that lucky?
要是没让他们发现我们 也许会牵出一起大案
If they didn't get onto us when they did, this might've been a hell of a case.
看你的了
It's on you.
偷袭? 发生在他的房间里?
Ambushed? In his own goddamn room?
是的 他会好起来 不过他...
Yeah, he gonna be all right, but he...
我才不在乎他会怎样 伙计
I don't give a fuck about how he gonna be, man.
你高价请来的世外高手
You put on out-of-town talent at a high price...
当然是期待他们能完成使命
you expect them to get the motherfucking job done.
他说我们之间的事...
He said that thing between us is...
他怎么说的 不需计较了
How did he put it? Absolved.
不需再计较了? 它妈的什么意思啊
Absolved? What the fuck do that mean?
Mouzone拍屁股走了 我们只会比他来之前更糟
Mouzone booked out, we worse off than when he came.
话传出去 说我们如此不堪一击...
If word gets out on the street that we weak like this...
我们还怎么把生意做下去?
how the fuck we supposed to maintain our shit?
我知道 我们是得反击 表明姿态
I know, but we gotta hit right back, make a statement.
但是Mouzone不肯说是谁干的
But Mouzone not saying who did this.
- 你问了他是谁? - 是的 我问了他
- You asked him who it was? - Yeah, I asked him.
- 为什么? - 什么为什么?
- Why? - Why what?
你怎么能问一个像Mouzone这样的硬汉 这样的问题呢?
How you gonna ask a soldier like Mouzone a question like that?
不管他说不说 他都会自己解决
Either he gonna say, or he gonna go and work it out.
无论怎样 你都不该问他
Either way, you ain't got to be asking him shit.
伙计 所有以市场为主导的行业都有周期
Man, every market-based business runs in cycles...
而我们现在正处在低谷期
and we going through a down-cycle right now.
String 这也跟你那狗屁商业课没关系
String, this ain't about your motherfucking business class either.
它们不一样 是两码事
It ain't that part of it. It's that other thing.
江湖就是江湖 永远如此
The street is the street. Always.
伙计 我们会挺过这难关的
Man, we gonna get through this bullshit anyway.
那还用说 你只要在我回去之前顶住了
No doubt. You just need to hold tight till I get uptown.
那天会来的 但在那之前...
And that day gonna come, but until then...
我们只有顺水推舟 顺势而为
we gotta do what we can do, when we can do it.
好吧 你去找"建议乔"吧
Yeah, you need to go to Prop Joe.
我不再跟你争了
I ain't gonna argue with you.
你觉得妥当就去做吧
You run it as you see fit.
起码在我回家之前 都你做主
At least until I get home, you do.
没意见
No doubt.
哥俩好
Us, man.
Us.
- 录像带太破了 - 它是多路合成
- Tape is fucked up. - It's multiplexed.
一种节省开支的办法
It's a way to save money.
不是1个摄影机录1盘录像带
Instead of one camera, one VCR...
而是10个摄影机录1盘录像带
it's 10 cameras playing on one VCR tape.
- 你能把这玩意儿整出点名堂来吗? - 没问题 用这软件就行
- Can you make sense of it? - Not a problem, with this software.
- 我们分解它就行了 - 分解?
- We just de-plex it. - De-plex?
让我给你们看看精华
Let me show you the highlight reel.
- 他是不是在亮警徽? - 看着像
- Is he flashing a badge? - Looks like it.
这不是你们能常看到的...
That's something you don't see too often...
执法人员开着奔驰跑
John Law in a Mercedes-Benz.
可能是我们的目标
That could be our boy.
还在镜头里
Head still on.
告诉我里面还有摄像头吧
Tell me we got cameras inside.
老天 我的裤子都湿了
Jesus, my pants are wet.
好啊 来吧 宝贝
Yeah. C'mon, baby.
好样的
Yeah.
货要迟一个星期
Re-up gonna be about a week or so late.
我的人在做些调整
My people are having to readjust to some shit.
一个星期?
A week?
他们说最晚那么久
No later than that, they say.
今天和Avon谈得如何?
How it go with Avon today?
很顺利
It's all good.
我们的老朋友
Our old friend.
有什么新闻?
What's the news?
港务警察正在监视一个 从Adriatica号下来的箱子
Port cops are sitting on a can that came off the Adriatica.
海关说里面都是毒品
Word around the customs shed, it's full of dope.
我是说Frank的事
I mean, about Frank.
- 区议会怎么说? - 先生们
- What's the district council saying? - Gentlemen.
Pakusa先生 鉴于你有官司缠身(尚未审理)
Mr. Pakusa, in light of your pending indictment...
我觉得你还是离这办公室越远越好
I'd think you'd stay as far away from this hall as possible.
你们没别的地方可去了吗?
Ain't y'all got some place to go?
只是想过来把话说清楚...
Just came to make it clear...
如果这里不开展自我整顿
that if there's no cleaning up in here...
这个工会将被取缔
this local will be decertified.
不用等到你们期满被赶走
Instead of your union running out of this office...
而是会有联邦法庭进行仲裁
it'll be a federal magistrate down the courthouse deciding things.
抓住机会选些新的头儿吧
Take the opportunity to elect new officers...
否则检察官会让这里关门大吉
or the US Attorney will padlock the door.
你们就只能在外面 眼巴巴看着里面
And you'll be outside, looking in.
一个人 一张票
One man, one vote.
Ott退出改选 以表对Sobotka的支持
"他有手吗? 他有脸吗?"
Did he have hands? Did he have a face?
"有? 那就不是我们干的"
Yes? Then it wasn't us.
你觉得这跟这个家伙...
You don't think that had anything to do...
...没有关系?
with this mope?
你这样做还不够哦  Lester
You gotta do better than that, Lester.
这个可怜蛋可没脸
This poor guy ain't got a face.
我有说DNA也对上了吗?
Did I mention the DNA matches?
这跟我没有任何关系
This has nothing to do with me.
这是那个保安吗?
Is that the security guard?
Walt Stokes 好人啊
Walt Stokes. A good man.
保存着详细记录
Keeps meticulous records.
Bunk 他们告诉我 这还能提高像素
Bunk, they tell me you can enhance each frame...
来让画面清晰
to get a clear look.
是吗? 示范给我看看
Yeah? Show it to me.
该死的 马里兰州的车牌
I'll be damned. Maryland tags.
JLY...
Juliet-Lima-Yankee...
5-4-5
5-4-5.
原来是BWI出租的
That comes back to a BWI rental.
我好奇是谁租的
I wonder who rented it.
这是暴利杀人和绑架
This is aggravated murder and kidnapping.
在这个州 罪可致死
In this state, it's a death penalty case.
我没有杀他
I didn't kill him.
我在场 但是没有杀他
I was there, but I didn't kill him.
Vondas干的
Vondas did.
他割了他的喉
He cut his throat.
看守人理应看守这些女人
The shepherd was supposed to watch over the women.
可是他却利用她们挣钱
Instead, he used them to make money.
其中一个女人 她反抗了 结果被杀了
One of the women, she fought. She was killed.
而这蠢货就杀光了剩下的 确保没有目击者
And this idiot kills the rest to make no witnesses.
他死有余辜
He had to die.
你想要咖啡还是汽水?
You want a coffee? Soda?
伏特加
Vodka.
咖啡
Coffee.
水落石出了 所有14件案子
They're down. All 14 of them.
因已知嫌犯已死而不再上诉
Abated by the untimely death of a known suspect.
还额外了结了一起无名男尸案 算是余兴节目
Plus another clearance on a John Doe case, just for laughs.
你想告诉Rawls吗?
You wanna tell Rawls?
让他再干等一阵子
Let him stew a while longer.
不过有一件事 我们得马上去做
One thing, though, we should do right away.
Vondas上面的人是谁?
Who's the man above Vondas?
"希腊人"
The Greek.
他叫什么?
What's his name?
如果你还希望能侥幸逃脱死刑
You want a chance at anything less than death row...
那你得马上告诉我们...
you're gonna tell me right now...
任何你知道的这些混蛋的下落
whatever it is you know about where those bastards might be.
在港口有个旅馆
A hotel at the harbor.
这个人的?
This one?
另一个
Another.
我可以带你们去
I can show you.
上
Go.
没人
Clear!
商务还是度假?
Business or pleasure for you?
生意 总是生意
Business. Always business.
- 你忘了什么? - 没什么大不了的
- What did you forget? - Nothing important.
唉呦 丢下我就来酒吧了?
You come to the bar without me?
小样找抽啊
Kiss my black cat's sister's ass.
- 出什么事了? - 案子查到头了
- What happened? - Case hit the wall.
怎么会?
How so?
Sobotka的侄子涉嫌走私和贩毒
The Sobotka nephew breaks for the smuggling and the drugs.
而俄罗斯人杀了那个 杀了那些姑娘们的凶手
The Russian breaks for the murder that fucking killed my girls.
而Vondopoulos和希腊人 我们都晚了一步
We were late on Vondopoulos and The Greek.
- 有多晚? - 让他们逃了
- How late? - They skipped.
我们发了跨州通缉令 但是那个Sobotka小子说
We got interstate flight warrants out, but from what the Sobotka kid says...
这些家伙有很多护照
these guys collect passports.
我们甚至不知道那个"希腊人"叫什么 对吧
We ain't even got a name for The Greek yet, right?
那案子里的毒品线索如何处理?
What're we doing with the drug end of the case?
我觉得我们可以把 Dixon和"建议乔"揭发给缉毒组
I guess we could offer up Dixon and Prop Joe to Narcotics.
看看他们想不想查下去
See if they want to follow through on their end.
我不知道
I don't know.
我不倒不会这么快放弃查Joe
I wouldn't be so quick to throw Joe back into the pond.
特侦组如果查查这个 应该会有不少乐趣 不是吗?
A major case squad could have some fun with that mess, don't you think?
警督
Lieutenant.
我从没跟你说过这事
I never told you this.
事实上 如果你把我要说的事说出去...
In fact, if you tell anyone I ever told you this...
我的前途就得在蒙大拿(美国西北部 地广人少)画上句号了
I'll finish my career in fucking Montana or some shit.
抱歉 借过
Excuse me, sorry.
不是你的人泄的秘
The leak wasn't your people.
当我到处打电话 查你那些目标时
When I called around looking for info on your targets...
我用的是联邦调查局的软件 这你知道的吧?
I used the FedCom software, you know?
我以为我是在跟一个 在San Diego的家伙讲话
I thought I was talking to some fuck in San Diego.
结果却是在华盛顿的反恐探员
The 911 boys in D.C.
我猜测Vondopoulos或是"希腊人" 对他们来说有用
I'm guessing Vondopoulos or The Greek was an asset to them.
反正是勾搭在一起了 我说不清 谁又知道呢?
Hooked up like, I don't know, who knows what?
我很抱歉 警督
I'm sorry, Lieutenant.
地球还在转 不是吗?
World just keeps turning, right?
你们去查新的案子 没人会回首
You guys move on to something new. No one looks back.
这轮我请
It's on me this time.
谁要?
Anyone?
你要去哪儿?
Where are you going?
上班
Work.
Frank 你这杂种
Frank, you cocksucker.
安息吧(波兰语)
Odpoczywaj w spokoju(Polish)
- 从这里我可以自己走 - 你确定?
- I can take it from here. - You sure?
没人敢在我们的地盘上捣乱
No one fucks with us on our turf.
它妈的我还能去哪儿 这儿怎么样?
Where the fuck else am I gonna go? How's it looking?
北码头有搜货船 老头子们都去了
One ROIRO at North Point. Graybeards grabbed that.
没别的活儿了
Nothing else today, really.
论资排辈最讨厌了
Seniority sucks.
谁让你不够辈分
If you ain't senior.
好吧 伙计
All right, man.
美国法警资产 此机构已停止营业 等候通知
* I was born my papa's son *
* A wanderin'eye and a smokin'gun *
* Now some of you would live through me *
* Lock me up and throw away the key *
* Or just find a place to hide away *
* Hope that I'll just go away *
* I feel alright *
* I feel alright tonight *
* I'll bring you precious contraband *
* And ancient tales from distant lands *
* Of conquerors and concubines and *
* Conjurers from darker times *
Grainary大厦(高层公寓楼)
今天对Baltimore来说意义非凡
This is a great day for Baltimore.
* Betrayal and conspiracy *
* Sacrilege and heresy *
* I feel alright *
* I feel alright tonight *
"希腊人"?
* I got every thing you want or need *
* Your darkest fear, your fondest dream *
* I ask you questions, tell you lies *
* Criticize and sympathize *
* Be careful what you wish for friend *
* Because I've been to hell and now I'm back again *
* I feel alright *
* I feel alright tonight *
玻璃窗上的海报:此房出售
* I got every thing you want or need *
* Your darkest fear, your fondest dream *
* I ask you questions, tell you lies *
* Criticize and sympathize *
* Be careful what you wish for,friend *
* Because I've been to hell and now I'm back again *
* I feel alright *
* I feel alright tonight *